Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection ca. 1982-1994 MSS 120 MSS.120
Fales Library and Special Collections
Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection
ca. 1950-1994
Fales Library and Special Collections
Ubu Repertory Theater
MSS.120
53 Linear Feet (34 boxes)
Ubu Repertory Theater, founded in 1982 by Franse (Francoise) Kourilsky, is the only US theater dedicated to presenting contemporary French-language plays in English translation. For its first ten years of existence, it operated from a small, second-floor theater in Chelsea and has since moved into offices at 95 Wall Street. Ubu has remained committed to cultural cross-fertilization as an essential element to the welfare of the theatrical community. The Ubu Repertory Theater Collection is comprised of plays, monologues, anthologies and criticism in French and English.
Provenance
The Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection was donated to the Fales Library in 2001.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical/Biographical Note:
Ubu Repertory Theater, founded in 1982 by Franse Kourilsky, is the only US theater dedicated to presenting contemporary French-language plays in English translation. An arena for cross-cultural exchange, Ubu calls on translators, playwrights, actors, directors and theater professionals to nurture international collaboration.
Ubu commissioned and published the first English translations of plays by well-known writers such as Aimire, Jean Tardieu, Simone Schwarz-Bart and Jean-Claude Grumberg. Ubu also introduced American readers to playwrights like Sony Labou Tansi, Bernard-Marie Koltand Tilly, all highly regarded in their own countries but just beginning to be known abroad.
In the last decade, Kourilsky took the idea of creating a theater that provides Americans with a unique window onto the stages of Francophone cultures, from Paris, Montreal, Brussels, Dakar, and Antanantarivo, to name a few. By making this new and challenging material accessible to Americans, Ubu has lived up to the inspiration of its name. As Ubu believes that cultural cross-fertilization is essential to the welfare of the theatrical community, it has no doubt strengthened the contemporary, international repertory.
After ten years of operating exclusively in a small, second-floor theater in Chelsea, Ubu Repertory Theater has moved into offices to 95 Wall Street and embarked on a series of larger Off-Broadway productions at the French Institute Alliance Franse's Florence Gould Hall and La MaMa E.T.C.'s Annex Theater. It also officially launched its own Ubu Bilingual Company. Since 1995, Ubu Repertory Theater has evolved a bilingual troupe as it presented critically-commended bilingual productions such as Jean-Paul Sartre's "Huis Clos/No Exit" (1985) and Albert Camus' "Le Malentendu/The Misunderstanding" and "Les Justes/The Just" (1998). The new company will also feature a design team whose ten-year body of work at Ubu will feature some of the most outstanding international theater productions in New York.
Scope and Content Note
The Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection is a part of the Downtown Collection at the Fales Library, New York University. The Fales Library is the primary special collections division of the NYU libraries, housing nearly 200,000 volumes of English and American literature from 1700 to the present. Strengths of the collection include the development of the English and American novel, with an emphasis on the Gothic and the Victorian novel.
The Ubu Repertory Theater Collection is comprised of plays, monologues, anthologies and criticism in French and English. Many of the manuscript submissions to Franse Kourilsky and the Ubu Repertory include correspondence, publicity brochures and articles pertaining to the playwrights and their work. Many of the works are by playwrights in exile, women writers, and francophone playwrights from around the world.
SERIES DESCRIPTION
Series 1: Plays in French: consists of plays and manuscripts in French which make up 23 boxes. They are listed in alphabetical order by author and by title when there is no author listed.
Series 2: Plays in English: made up of plays and manuscripts in English and French-language plays in English translation. Series 2 contains 10 boxes. Translators and adaptors are listed on the folder only. Series 2 is also listed in alphabetical order or by title if there is no author.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by author heading.
The files are grouped into two series.
Missing Title
Series I: French Manuscripts
Series II: English Manuscripts
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Theater |x History |y 20th century.; French drama |y 20th century.; New York (N.Y.).; French drama |x Translations into English.; Scripts (documents); Kourilsky, Françoise
- Series I: French Manuscripts
  - Abelar, Georges. 'Le supporter', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 1)
  - Abomo-Mvondo/Maurin, Marie-Rose. 'La lettre', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 2)
  - Adam, Pascal. 'Avant le silence du fleuve', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 3)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Le ping pong', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 4)
  - Adamov, Arthur. 'Le Professeur Taranne', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 5)
  - Adelis, Mylene. 'Le cabaret du chat noir', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 6)
  - Adjibi, Jean-Baptiste. 'Reponses insolubles', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 7)
  - Adler, Yves. 'La nuit derni', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 8)
  - Akerman, Chantal. 'Hall de nuit', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 9)
  - d'Albon Azimioara, Ada. 'En sense inverse', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 10)
  - d'Albon Azimioara, Ada. 'Entre le rien et l'infini la terre pourrait e carr, undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 11)
  - d'Albon Azimioara, Ada. 'Le chat empaill/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 12)
  - Aledji, Ousmane. 'L' oi mal', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 13)
  - Alemdjrodo, Kankoue. 'Les mauvaises graines', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 14)
  - Allegret, C. and Borras, E. 'Trois fois rien', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 15)
  - Amette, Jacques-Pierre. 'Le maitre-nageur', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 16)
  - Amette, Jacques-Pierre. 'Passions secretes, crimes d'avril', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 17)
  - Amoni, Emmanuelle. 'La depan'heure', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 18)
  - Anciaux, Rapha 'Bluff', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 19)
  - Anouilh, Jean. (adaptor). 'Antigone', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 20)
  - Anouilh, Jean. 'L'hurluberlu ou le rtionnaire amoureux', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 21)
  - Anouilh, Jean. 'Ornifle ou le courant d'air', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 22)
  - Anouilh, Jean. 'Romet Jeannette', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 23)
  - Anthony, Jean-Pierre. 'Le festin des ogres', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 24)
  - Anthony, Jean-Pierre. 'Toros', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 25)
  - Aouad Basbous, Therese. 'Seuls comme l'eau', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 26)
  - Apostolides, Jean-Marie. 'En attendant Beckett ou ceci n'est pas une pi', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 27)
  - Apostolides, Jean-Marie. 'L'oeil crev/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 28)
  - Arnoux, Stane. 'Soldat de plomb', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 29)
  - Arnoux, Stane. 'Temps mort', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 30)
  - Arnoux, Stane. 'Terre promise', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 31)
  - Aron, Jean-Paul. 'P-grand', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 32)
  - Asseng, Protais. 'L'homme-femme', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 33)
  - Asseng, Protais. 'Le thre de l'empire', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 34)
  - Athea, Brigitte. 'Instants de femmes', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 35)
  - Athea, Brigitte. 'Soliloque', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 36)
  - Atlan, Liliane. 'Les de bonheur', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 37)
  - Atlan, Liliane. 'Les musiciens, les emigrants', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 38)
  - Atlan, Liliane. 'Un op pour Terezin (not the play)', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 39)
  - Atlan, Liliane. 'Un op pour Terezin', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 40)
  - Atlan, Liliane. 'Les passants un livre ire', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 41)
  - Atlan, Liliane. 'Le troisi verre de vin, ou troisi ouverture', undated; 31142040610209 (Box I.1, Folder 42)
  - Aveline, Claude. 'Le bestiaire inattendu', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 43)
  - Avron, Philippe. 'Ma cour d'honneur', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 44)
  - BAmadou A. 'Kara', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 45)
  - Badami, Claude. 'Juste pour voir ce que fait', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 46)
  - Baker, Leandre-Alain. 'Les jours se trainentles nuits aussi', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 47)
  - Ballini, Georges. 'Cosmos, pain quotidien', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 48)
  - Ballini, Georges. 'Mars, premi phase', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 49)
  - Bart, Reine. 'Le cercle des evasions', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 50)
  - Bart, Reine. 'Dans le salon d'Emilie ou Voltaire ira-t-il sur la lune?', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 51)
  - Bart, Reine. 'Le dr du Figuier', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 52)
  - Bart, Reine. 'Le dr du Figuier (incomplete)', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 53)
  - Bart, Reine. 'Le dompteur ou la fordes traverses', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 54)
  - Bart, Reine. 'L'homme aimes femmes (version 1)', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 55)
  - Bart, Reine. 'L'homme aimes femmes (version 2)', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 56)
  - Bart, Reine. 'L'Orphelinat', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 57)
  - Bart, Reine. 'Ouverture sur mer', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 58)
  - Bart, Reine. 'La place de la libert/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 59)
  - Barthmy, Maurice-Domingue. 'J'ai passa vie hercher l'ouvre-bos', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 60)
  - Bartoli, Daniel. 'L'exactitude des somnambules', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 61)
  - Batista, Mario. 'Trois visages dans une chevelure', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 62)
  - Bats, Isabelle. 'Effet de bande', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 63)
  - Baean-Louis. 'Le chat de nemesis', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 64)
  - Baean-Louis. 'Jules et Lise', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 65)
  - Baean-Louis. 'Pourquoi aujourd'hui?', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 66)
  - Bazot, Xavier. 'Mrial, ple et biscuits', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 67)
  - Beauvais, Marc. 'Les trois vies', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 68)
  - Beavoir, Simone de. 'Monologue', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 69)
  - Bec, Frric. 'Le bon, la brute et le nt', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 70)
  - Beckers, Walter. 'La f Raquel', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 71)
  - Buet, Arnaud. 'Kinkali', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 72)
  - Bellay, Jenny. 'A la belle saison', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 73)
  - Bemba, Sylvain. 'L'etrange crime de Monsieur Pancrace Amadeus', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 74)
  - Bemba, Sylvain. 'Noces posthumes de Santigone', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 75)
  - Bemba, Sylvain. 'Qu'est devenu Ignoumba le Chasseur?', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 76)
  - Ben Aa, Dominique. Chiasma, undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 76a.)
  - Benedetto, Andr'Djebel Amour', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 77)
  - Benedetto, Andr'Trois pieces pour un couple', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 78)
  - Benguettaf, M'Hamed. 'Fatma', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 79)
  - Bensoussan, Georges. 'Est-ouest', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 80)
  - Bergot, Vale. 'Paume's troquet ou fais pas ta fi avec Jean-Jacques', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 81)
  - Beriouni, Amid. 'L'arbre du desert', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 82)
  - Beriouni, Amid. 'Les eaux noires de la nuit', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 83)
  - Berjaud, Jme-Elie. 'Don Juan ahiti', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 84)
  - Bernard-Villa, Nicole. 'La poupde chiffon', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 85)
  - BerthommLuce and le Guillochet, Christian. 'La noce', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 86)
  - Bertrand, Franck. 'La liason mathematique', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 87)
  - Bertrand, Franck. 'La liason mathematique', undated; 31142040610217 (Box I.2, Folder 88)
  - Besnehard, Daniel. 'L'affaire des nuits', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 89)
  - Besnehard, Daniel. 'Cong, undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 90)
  - Besnehard, Daniel. 'Hudson River: Un dr d'exil', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 91)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'L' de femme de Marie Hasparren', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 92)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'Baron ou Le vertige et le gounittitle>, undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 93)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'Baron ou Le vertige et le goodified)', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 94)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'Commentaire d'amour', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 95)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'F foreign', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 96)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'Grande le', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 97)
  - Besset, Jean-Marie. 'Mais, mon cheri, que pensez-vous de Jean-Pierre?', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 98)
  - Beucher, Fabrice. 'Dieu! Que la terre est basse!', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 99)
  - Beugras, Henri. 'Croisi de r', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 100)
  - Bienvenue, Yvan. 'Rement de contes', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 101)
  - Biget, Philippe. 'Scriptodrame', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 102)
  - Bilder, Nicolas. 'Conditionnelle', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 103)
  - Billetdoux, Frans. 'Le comportement des epoux Bredburry', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 104)
  - Blasband, Philippe. 'Bruxelles-Central', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 105)
  - Blasband, Philippe. 'Ou es-tu, Sammy Rebenski?', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 106)
  - Bloch, Bernard. 'Le prince et le marchand', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 107)
  - Blutch, Herv'Monsieur Paul n'est pas commun', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 108)
  - Blutch, Herv'Le professionnel', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 109)
  - Bluteau, Bernard. 'Plus vite que les balles', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 110)
  - Bodelin, Bodi Banch. 'Le compte-rendu', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 111)
  - Bohbot, Albert. 'La consume', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 112)
  - Bohbot, Albert. 'La terre que je connais', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 113)
  - Boileau, Chantale. 'La mort de blanche', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 114)
  - Bon, Frans. 'Vie de Myriam C.', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 115)
  - Bonal, Denise. 'Turbulances et petits dils', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 116)
  - Bonal, Denise. 'Une femme sans consequence', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 117)
  - Bonal, Denise. 'Feroce comme le coeur', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 118)
  - Bonal, Denise. 'Les moutons de la nuit', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 119)
  - Bonal, Denise. 'On n'est pas a la noce', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 120)
  - Bonal, Denise. 'Les pas perdus', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 121)
  - Bopoungo, Jean Carltetto. 'Le secret des immortels', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 122)
  - Borlon, Jean-Pierre. 'Un coin de paradis', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 123)
  - Borlon, Jean-Pierre. 'Emily ou le chant impossible', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 124)
  - Boronad, Philippe et Vale. 'Le voyage immobile', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 125)
  - Bouchard, Michel Marc. 'Le chemin des passes-dangereuses, trage routiere', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 126)
  - Bouchard, Michel Marc. 'Le contre-nature de Chrysippe Tanguay, ecologiste', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 127)
  - Bouchet, Maud. 'Le linge sale', undated; 31142040610225 (Box I.3, Folder 128)
  - Boudon, Michel. 'Insondable, voile qu'est la nuit', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 129)
  - Boulva, Josette and Gatard, Marie. 'Ma ch Rose', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 130)
  - Boumaour, Eldja. 'La nounou de Fatima', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 131)
  - Bourdon, Jean-Louis. 'Derri les collines', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 132)
  - Bourgeade, Pierre. 'L'aigle et le serpent', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 133)
  - Bourgeade, Pierre. 'Le passeport', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 134)
  - Bourgeade, Pierre. 'La porte', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 135)
  - Bourgeyx, Claude. 'Darling', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 136)
  - Bourgeyx, Claude. 'L'homme aux gants gris', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 137)
  - Bourgeyx, Claude. 'La ligne 28', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 138)
  - Bourquin, Elie. 'Lapin lapin', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 139)
  - Bowles, Jane. 'Sous la tonnelle', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 140)
  - Bowles, Jane. 'Sous la tonnelle', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 141)
  - Brisville, Jean-Claude. 'Saint-Just', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 142)
  - Buffard, Claude-Henri. 'Une nuit d'hiver, sans rien dessus', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 143)
  - Burgaud, Jean Pierre. 'Fragments no. 1', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 144)
  - Buyens, Frans. 'Sarah ditLeila dit', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 145)
  - Calveyr, Arnaldo. 'Le nombre de la b', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 146)
  - Camus, Albert. 'Les justes', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 147)
  - Camus, Albert. 'Le Malentendu', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 148)
  - Caro, Christian. 'Eclipse', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 149)
  - Castay, Bernadette. 'Seulement les jours', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 150)
  - Caudron, Hughes. 'Pouvoir de Pierre', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 151)
  - Crier, Agn 'Tableaux', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 152)
  - Centre de Crivit'itions lettristes', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 153)
  - Cerasi, Graciela. 'Stockage provisoire', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 154)
  - Cervantes, Frans and Ruel, Francine. 'Le dernier quatuor d'un homme sourd', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 155)
  - Cire, Aim'Cahier d'un retour au pays natal', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 156)
  - Cesaire, Ina. 'Les passantes du fort de France populaire', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 157)
  - Cesaire, Ina. 'Pluie et vent sur telummiracle', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 158)
  - Cesaire, Ina. 'Rosanie soleil', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 159)
  - Cesaire, Mich. 'L'annde tous les saints', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 160)
  - Cesaire, Mich. 'Bal d'eventails', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 161)
  - Chaffin, Frans. 'Ma norvegienne, soluble dans l'eau', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 162)
  - Chaffin, Frans. 'Plus tendre est la baleine', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 163)
  - Chalem, Denise. 'A cinquante ans elle duvrait la mer', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 164)
  - Chalem, Denise. 'La nuit de cristal', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 165)
  - Chalem, Denise. 'Prague1094 kms', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 166)
  - Chalem, Denise. 'Le temps arr', undated; 31142040610233 (Box I.4, Folder 167)
  - Chang, Kwee Fong Khee Fah Kong Luin. 'Quand vinrent les voisins', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 168)
  - Charlier, Jacques Rey. 'Entrrelativ: Patchwork & Cerezo Rosa', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 169)
  - Charlier, Jacques Rey. 'Entrrelativ: Lazare Lezard', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 170)
  - Charmentant, Christian. 'Impasse priv/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 171)
  - Charneux, Olivier. 'Le veilleur', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 172)
  - Charneux, Olivier. 'Les vieux os', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 173)
  - Charras, Charles. 'La nuit du roi ou je vais dormir croyez-moi', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 174)
  - Charras, Charles. 'Je vais dormir, croyez-moi', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 175)
  - Chauchat, Andr'La nuit du 4 aounittitle>, undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 176)
  - Chaurette, Normand. 'Les reines', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 177)
  - Chaurette, Normand. 'Petit navire', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 178)
  - Cheng, Xing Xing. 'R rouge', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 179)
  - Chenus, Sylvie. 'Le moulin zinzolin', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 180)
  - Chenus, Sylvie. 'Saga de la gare du nord', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 181)
  - Chesnot, Pierre. 'A vos souhaits', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 182)
  - Chichportich, Myriam. 'Une paix de cochon', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 183)
  - Chodat, Frans. 'Le dnage', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 184)
  - Chodat, Frans. 'Une femme presque comme les autres', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 185)
  - Chodat, Frans. 'Miniature en flamme', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 186)
  - Chorfi, Mo. 'Ava-Clark-Grace-Gary et les autres', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 187)
  - Chraibi, Driss. 'D'autres voix', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 188)
  - Cisse, Ahmed Tidjani. '1789 en l'isle St-Louis du Senegal', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 189)
  - Cixous, Hne. '[untitled]', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 190)
  - Cixous, Hne. 'On ne part pas, on ne revient pas', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 191)
  - Cixous, Hne. 'Sakundeva', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 192)
  - Claing, Robert. 'Les fossiles', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 193)
  - de la Clergerie, Catherine. 'Les jeudis d'Elio Lehner', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 194)
  - de la Clergerie, Catherine. 'Le loup de bois de Meudon', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 195)
  - de la Clergerie, Catherine. 'Padi pado la sorci du TGV', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 196)
  - Cloutier, Guy. 'La statue de fer', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 197)
  - Coffy, Didier. 'L'extion', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 198)
  - Cohen, Daniel and Culiersi, Jean-Marc. 'Une vie de prince', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 199)
  - Colas, Hubert. 'Nomades', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 200)
  - Colas, Hubert. 'Terre ou l'epopsauvage de Gult Matteo', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 201)
  - Colas, Hubert. 'Traces suivi de la br', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 202)
  - Colas, Hubert. 'Visages', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 203)
  - Collas, Philippe. 'Criminel tango', undated; 31142040610241 (Box I.5, Folder 204)